Leslie Crow Papers
Holt-Atherton Department of Special Collections
Leslie Crow papers
1850-2006
1978-2006
MSS 316
Crow, Leslie Ellen (1954-2006)
25 linear feet
University of the Pacific. Library. Holt-Atherton Dept. of Special Collections Stockton, California 95211
Collection consists of materials collected and written by Leslie Crow primarily concerning local history and historic preservation in California.
Access
Collection open for research.
Biography / Administrative History
Stockton, California, resident Leslie Ellen Crow was a local historian, archivist, and civic activist. Born in Kenosha, Wisconsin, on April 11, 1954, she graduated from high school in Des Plaines, Illinois, in 1972, and moved to California the following year. After attending Santa Monica College from 1973 to 1975, she entered the University of the Pacific in 1976. Two years later, she received a bachelor's degree in history with honors.
In 1979, Crow entered the graduate program in history at the University of the Pacific. Although she never finished, the program led to her involvement in an oral history project conducted by the California Youth Authority. This launched her career in public history, or the practice of history in non-scholarly settings. In subsequent years, she held jobs as Historic Inventory Coordinator for the City of Vacaville (1979-80), Historic Preservation Specialist for the Central Sierra Planning Council (1980-82), and Archivist for the Bank of Stockton (1991-98). From 1980 to 2006, she also worked intermittently as a freelance researcher and consultant.
As a consultant, Crow conducted research to designate as Stockton City Landmarks the First Church of Christ, Scientist; the Philomathean Club; and Stockton Children's Home. Among other projects, she also spearheaded efforts to nominate as California Historical Landmarks the Lockeford, California, Schoolhouse, and Stockton's Western Pacific Depot. Crow's efforts also proved crucial in placing on the National Register of Historic Places the California Building (Stockton); Commercial and Savings Bank (Stockton); Quarters A, Albert Lindley Residence, U.S. Navy, Rough and Ready Island; Stockton's Little Manila neighborhood and Sikh Temple, and the Woodbridge, California, Masonic Lodge. In addition, she conducted surveys of historic resources for the City of Ripon, California, and Sacramento, and did historical studies of Stockton's City Hall and Stockton State Hospital's Superintendent's Residence in preparation for renovation.
In 1989, Crow was appointed to Stockton's Cultural Heritage Board, which she chaired from 1990 to 2006. Her appointment exposed her to revitalization efforts aimed at Stockton's aging inner city and waterfront. It also gave her a platform to promote historic preservation and plunged her into a period of civic activism. During the 1990s, she served on Stockton's Women Veterans' Memorial Task Force, the Friends of the Fox Theatre, the Mayor's Waterfront Revival Task Force, the Stockton Waterfront Committee, the Fundraising Committee for the Weber Point Events Center, the City of Stockton Sesquicentennial Committee, and Stockton Mid-Town Task Force. Meanwhile, she also held membership on the College of the Pacific Alumni Advisory Council and served in a variety of voluntary positions at the San Joaquin County Historical Society.
Crow died in May 2006, at the zenith of her career.
Scope and Content of Collection
Collection consists of materials collected and written by Leslie Crow. Of special interest are its research files, whose contents range widely from maps, plans, photocopied newspaper articles, and handwritten notes, to photographs, slides, and applications for historic registration. Geographically, the focus varies from Alameda, Calaveras, and San Francisco Counties to Lodi and the City of Sacramento. However, the richest, fullest, and most numerous files involve Stockton and San Joaquin County.
Arrangement
Collection is organized into six series: 1. Biographical Files; 2. Voluntary Service Records; 3. Research Files; 4. VHS Cassettes; 5. Oversize; and 6. Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Alameda County (Calif.) - History; Alpine County (Calif.) - History; Amador County (Calif.) - History; Calaveras County (Calif.) - History; Calaveras River Watershed; California Youth Authority; Historic preservation - California; Lockeford (Calif.); Lodi (Calif.) - History; Ripon (Calif.); Sacramento (Calif.) - History; San Francisco (Calif.) - History; San Joaquin County (Calif.) - History; San Joaquin County Historical Society; Solano County (Calif.) - History; Stockton (Calif.) - History; Stockton (Calif.) - Politics and government; Trinity County (Calif.) - History; Tuolumne County (Calif.) - History; Yosemite National Park (Calif.) - History
Separated Material
Records of the Stockton Cultural Heritage Board have been removed from this collection and added to the Stockton Cultural Heritage Board Papers, 1977-2005, MSS 210.
Container List:
- Series I: Biographical Files, 1978-2006
  Includes plaques, certificates, diplomas, forms, newspaper clippings, correspondence, brochures, journal articles, photographs, and resumes.
  - Box 1
    - 1.1 Awards and Diplomas (1 of 4)
    - 1.2 Awards and Diplomas (2 of 4)
    - 1.3 Awards and Diplomas (3 of 4)
    - 1.4 Awards and Diplomas (4 of 4)
    - 1.5 Memorial Service
    - 1.6 Portfolio (1 of 4)
    - 1.7 Portfolio (2 of 4)
    - 1.8 Portfolio (3 of 4)
    - 1.9 Portfolio (4 of 4)
    - 1.10 Resumes
    - 1.11 Women of the Year Nomination
    - 1.12 Writings and Presentations
- Series II: Voluntary Service Records, 1883-2004
  Consists of three Subseries: 1. Sacramento; 2. San Joaquin Historical Society; and 3. City of Stockton and San Joaquin County.
  - Box 1 (cont.)
    - Subseries: Sacramento, 1999
      Includes brochures, newspaper clippings, announcements, correspondence, notes, and photographs.
      - 1.13 Gold Fever!
      - 1.14 Gold Fever!-Photographs
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Gold Fever! 1999
    - Subseries: San Joaquin County Historical Society, 1883-1999
      Includes correspondence, memos, photocopied research, presentations, articles, meeting minutes, agendas, promotional literature, newsletters, announcements, inventories, photographs, membership rosters, guidebooks, newsletters, financial documents, reports, newspaper clippings, announcements, bylaws, certificates, and monographs.
      - 1.15 Annual Report, 1991
      - 1.16 Annual Reports, 1985-1989
      - 1.17 Annual Reports, 1990-1998
      - 1.18 Barbeque, 1989
      - 1.19 Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1990-1994 (1 of 3)
      - 1.20 Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1990-1994 (2 of 3)
      - 1.21 Board of Trustees and Executive Committee, 1990-1994 (3 of 3)
      - 1.22 Board of Trustees Handbook, undated
      - 1.23 Bylaws, 1988-1989
      - 1.24 Construction and Groundbreaking
      - 1.25 Correspondence, 1986-1992
  - Box 2
    - Subseries: San Joaquin County Historical Society, 1883-1999 (cont.)
      - 2.1 Docent Council, 1987-1991
      - 2.2 Docent Council Public Relations, 1990-1991
      - 2.3 Golden Acorn Award, 1990-1991
      - 2.4 Land of Bright Promise monograph, 1990
      - 2.5 Membership Rosters, 1990 and undated
      - 2.6 News and Notes, 1985-1987
      - 2.7 News and Notes, 1988
      - 2.8 News and Notes, 1989-1990
      - 2.9 News and Notes, 1991-1992
      - 2.10 News and Notes, 1993-1994
      - 2.11 Presentations, 1987-1991
      - 2.12 Publications Committee, 1986-1994 (1 of 2)
      - 2.13 Publications Committee, 1986-1994 (2 of 2)
      - 2.14 Publicity, 1986-1993
      - 2.15 San Joaquin Historian, 1981-1989
      - 2.16 San Joaquin Historian, 1990-1993
      - 2.17 San Joaquin Historian, 1994-1997
      - 2.18 San Joaquin Historian, 1998-1999
      - 2.19 Special Events-Museum, 1988-1991 (1 of 2)
      - 2.20 Special Events-Museum, 1988-1991 (2 of 2)
      - 2.21 Special Events-Museum, Undated
      - 2.22 Sponsor Programs, 1990-1992
      - 2.23 Tours, 1992
      - 2.24 Valley Days, 1988-1990
      - 2.25 Various Publications, 1986-1993
      - 2.26 Victorian Christmas, 1988-1989
      - 2.27 Victorian Christmas, 1989-Public Relations
  - Box 3
    - Subseries: San Joaquin County Historical Society, 1883-1999 (cont.)
      - 3.1 Victorian Christmas, 1990
      - 3.2 Victorian Cookery and Christmas Traditions, 1990
      - 3.3 Weber Homesite Opening, 1991 (1 of 2)
      - 3.4 Weber Homesite Opening, 1991 (2 of 2)
      - 3.5 Unsorted Notes and Documents, 1883-1994
    - Subseries: City of Stockton and San Joaquin County, 1991-2004
      Includes correspondence, memos, photocopied research, presentations, articles, meeting minutes, agendas, promotional literature, maps, newsletters, announcements, inventories, and photographs.
      - 3.6 Central Stockton Revitalization Committee, 1991-1992
      - 3.7 CSUS Stockton Midtown Revitalization Strategy Advisory Group, 1999-2000
      - 3.8 CSUS Stockton Midtown Revitalization Strategy Advisory Group, 2000 (1 of 2)
      - 3.9 CSUS Stockton Midtown Revitalization Strategy Advisory Group, 2000 (2 of 2)
      - 3.10 CSUS Stockton Midtown Revitalization Strategy Advisory Group, 2000-2003
      - 3.11 CSUS Stockton Midtown Revitalization Strategy Advisory Group, 2001
      - 3.12 CSUS Stockton Midtown Revitalization Strategy Advisory Group, 2001-2002
      - 3.13 Downtown Stockton Alliance, 1997 (1 of 2)
      - 3.14 Downtown Stockton Alliance, 1997 (2 of 2)
      - 3.15 Downtown Stockton Alliance, 1997-2002 (1 of 3)
      - 3.16 Downtown Stockton Alliance, 1997-2002 (2 of 3)
      - 3.17 Downtown Stockton Alliance, 1997-2002 (3 of 3)
  - Box 4
    - Subseries: City of Stockton and San Joaquin County, 1991-2004 (cont.)
      - 4.1 Downtown Stockton Alliance, 1998-1999
      - 4.2 Downtown Stockton Alliance, 1998-2002
      - 4.3 Downtown Stockton Alliance, undated
      - 4.4 Friends of the Fox, 1998-1999
      - 4.5 Magnolia Advisory Committee, 1991-2002
      - 4.6 Safe Neighborhood Action Group, 1996-1999
      - 4.7 San Joaquin County Office of Education, 1999
      - 4.8 Stockton Beautiful, 1993-1997
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Stockton Beautiful Publicity
      - (Transferred to MSS210, Stockton Cultural Heritage Board Papers) Stockton Cultural Heritage Board
      - 4.9 Stockton Firefighters Relief Association, 1997
      - 4.10 Stockton Public Art Inventory, 2000
      - 4.11 Stockton Sesquicentennial Committee, 1997-1999 (1 of 2)
      - 4.12 Stockton Sesquicentennial Committee, 1997-1999 (2 of 2)
      - 4.13 Time Capsule Committee, 2000 (1 of 2)
      - 4.14 Time Capsule Committee, 2000 (2 of 2)
      - 4.15 Time Capsule Images
      - 4.16 Waterfront Committee, 1998
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Waterfront Task Force
      - 4.17 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1995 (1 of 5)
      - 4.18 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1995 (2 of 5)
      - 4.19 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1995 (3 of 5)
      - 4.20 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1995 (4 of 5
      - 4.21 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1995 (5 of 5)
      - 4.22 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1996 (1 of 2)
      - 4.23 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1996 (2 of 2)
      - 4.24 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1997
      - 4.25 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1998
      - 4.26 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1999 (1 of 2)
      - 4.27 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 1999 (2 of 2)
  - Box 5
    - Subseries: City of Stockton and San Joaquin County, 1991-2004 (cont.)
      - 5.1 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 2000-2001
      - 5.2 Waterfront Revival Task Force, 2002-2004
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Waterfront Revival Task Force, Fundraising Lists, 1999
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Waterfront Revival Task Force, Maps, 1850-2000
      - 5.3 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (1 of 7)
      - 5.4 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (2 of 7)
      - 5.5 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (3 of 7)
      - 5.6 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (4 of 7)
      - 5.7 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (5 of 7)
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (6 of 7)
      - 5.8 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1995 (7 of 7)
      - 5.9 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (1 of 8
      - 5.10 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (2 of 8)
      - 5.11 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (3 of 8)
      - 5.12 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (4 of 8)
      - 5.13 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (5 of 8)
      - 5.14 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (6 of 8)
      - 5.15 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (7 of 8)
      - 5.16 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1996 (8 of 8)
      - 5.17 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, 1997
      - 5.18 Waterfront Revival Task Force, Reports and Proposals, Undated
      - 5.19 Womens Veteran Memorial Task Force, 1992-1993
- Series III: Research Files, 1850-2006
  Consists of eighteen subseries: 1. Alameda County, 2. Alpine County, 3. Amador County, 4. Calaveras County, 5. Calaveras River Watershed, 6. California Youth Authority, 7. Central Sierra Planning Council, 8. Lockeford, 9. Lodi American Viticultural Area (LAVA), 10. Ripon, 11. Sacramento, 12. San Francisco County and City, 13. San Joaquin County, 14. Solano County, 15, Stockton, 16. Trinity County, 17. Tuolumne County, 18. Yosemite National Park.
  - Box 6
    - Subseries: Alameda County, 1938-2002
      Includes meeting notes, promotional brochure, proposal for professional services, photocopied newspaper and articles.
      - 6.1 Altamont
      - 6.2 Livermore
    - Subseries: Alpine County, 1951-1981
      Includes handwritten, typed, and photocopied notes, maps, historic site surveys, report on archaeological and historical setting, photocopied chapters, and photographs.
      - 6.3 Alpine County
    - Subseries: Amador County, 1881-2005
      Includes correspondence, newspaper clippings and photocopies, address lists, handwritten and photocopied research notes, evaluations of cultural resources, consulting proposals and reports, maps, travel brochures, and photographs.
      - 6.4 Amador County
      - 6.5 Amador County Hospital-Historical Finding
      - 6.6 Amador County Hospital-Jackson
      - 6.7 Gold Rush Ranch and Golf Course
      - 6.8 Preston School of Industry, Ione
      - 6.9 Silver Lake History
      - 6.10 Sutter Creek
      - 6.11 Sutter Creek-Data Sheets Completed
      - 6.12 Vintage Estates
      - 6.13 Vintage Estates-Cultural Resources Survey
    - Subseries: Calaveras County, 1871-2005
      Includes correspondence, newspaper articles, handwritten notes, evaluations of cultural resources, consulting proposal and reports, maps, applications for designation as officially recognized historic resources, studies of historic properties, locations, and structures, membership lists, term papers, and photographs.
      - 6.14 Angels Camp
      - 6.15 Calaveras County
      - 6.16 Calaveras County Archives
      - 6.17 Calaveras County Historical Society
      - 6.18 Calaveras Indigent Cemetery
      - 6.19 Calaveras Indigent Cemetery-Cultural Resource Investigation
      - (See Oversize, Box 24) Copperopolis Maps
      - 6.20 Copperopolis Proposal
      - 6.21 Copperopolis, Reeds Turnpike, OByrnes Ferry Road-Historic Context
      - 6.22 Maps
      - 6.23 Mark Twain District Hospital
      - 6.24 Mokelumne Hill
      - 6.25 Mokelumne Hills Site: ASI
      - 6.26 Murphys
      - 6.27 Oak Canyon Historical Context
      - 6.28 San Andreas
      - 6.29 Southwest Corner
      - 6.30 Wallace-Nakashima Residence
      - 6.31 Wallace Residence: ASI
      - 6.32 Valley Springs
  - Box 7
    - Subseries: Calaveras River Watershed / East Stockton Water District, 1852-2005
      Includes correspondence, newspaper clippings and photocopies, handwritten notes, evaluations of cultural resources, consulting agreement, maps, drafts of book, and agency minutes and announcements.
      - 7.1 Book Proposal
      - 7.2 Cultural Resources Investigation, 2001
      - 7.3 History of Calaveras River Watershed, Draft 1
      - 7.4 History of Calaveras River Watershed, Draft 2
      - 7.5 New Hogan Dam
      - 7.6 Research (1 of 2)
      - 7.7 Research (2 of 2)
      - 7.8 Stockton East Water Districtl
      - 7.9 Stockton East Water District-Press Coverage
    - Subseries: California Youth Authority, 1889-1980
      Includes correspondence, resource material, research notes, memoranda, oral histories, photographs, published articles and journals, and reports.
      - 7.10 Bibliography
      - 7.11 Correspondence and Instructions
      - 7.12 Notes (1 of 3)
      - 7.13 Notes (2 of 3)
      - 7.14 Notes (3 of 3)
      - 7.15 Oral History-R. G. Harvey
      - 7.16 Oral History-Paul J. McKusick
      - 7.17 Oral History-W. L. Tregoning
      - 7.18 Oral History-Iris Walden
      - 7.19 Pacific Historian Article
      - 7.20 Reports on Research
      - 7.21 Resource Material (1 of 4)
      - 7.22 Resource Material (2 of 4)
      - 7.23 Resource Material (3 of 4)
      - 7.24 Resource Material (4 of 4)
    - Subseries: Central Sierra Planning Council, 1879-1982
      Includes correspondence, map, receipts, instructions, survey questionnaire, grant proposal, draft agreement, research notes and reports, inventories, and preservation and volunteer guidelines.
      - 7.25 Administrative Material
      - 7.26 Correspondence
      - 7.27 Reports
      - 7.28 Resource Material
      - 7.29 Training Manual Resources
      - 7.30 Volunteer Workbook
  - Box 8
    - Subseries: Lockeford, 1862-2005
      Includes correspondence, business proposals, newspaper articles, contracts, research notes, business cards, meeting agendas, maps, invitations for bids, photographs, invoices, applications for grants and historic registration, plans, and assessments.
      - 8.1 Consulting Proposal
      - 8.2 Grant Contract-LCSD and SHPO
      - 8.3 Lockeford Community Services Districtl
      - 8.4 Lockeford-Harmony Grove
      - 8.5 Lockeford-Press Coverage
      - 8.6 Lockeford-Research
      - 8.7 Lockeford School: Bid Docs. Phase I
      - 8.8 Lockeford School Foundation Project
      - 8.9 Lockeford School-Foundation Project Status
      - 8.10 Lockeford School Grants
      - 8.11 Lockeford Schoolhouse-LDA
      - 8.12 Lockeford School-Phase II
      - 8.13 Lockeford School: Phase II (Roof)
      - (See Oversize, Box 24) Lockeford School Plans
      - 8.14 Lockeford School Registration
      - 8.15 Lockeford School Registration Nomination
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Lockeford School, Renovation Plans, 2003
      - 8.16 Lockeford School RFP
      - 8.17 Lockeford School RFP Architectural (1 of 2)
      - 8.18 Lockeford School RFP Architectural (2 of 2)
      - 8.19 Lockeford School RFP: Toxics Survey
      - 8.20 Lockeford School: West Coast Environmental
      - 8.21 Lockeford School: Photographs and Slides
      - 8.22 Unsorted Notes and Research
    - Subseries: Lodi American Viticultural Area (LAVA), 1861-2003
      Includes correspondence, brochures, meeting agendas, petitions and petition responses, newspaper articles, maps, research notes, historical findings, photographs, and pamphlets.
      - 8.23 Alta Mesa
      - 8.24 Borden Ranch
      - 8.25 Clements Hills
      - 8.26 Deer Creek Hills
      - 8.27 Historical Findings
      - 8.28 LAVA Group
      - 8.29 Petition to BATF
      - 8.30 Petition Responses
      - 8.31 Photographs
      - 8.32 Publications
      - 8.33 Research
  - Box 9
    - Subseries: Ripon, 1846-2004
      Includes correspondence, newspaper clippings and photocopies, photographs, digital images, 35 mm slides, handwritten notes, applications and paperwork in support of designation as officially recognized historic resources, studies of historic properties, structures, and neighborhoods, guides to historic resources, consulting agreement, maps, and listings of historic resources.
      - 9.1 Chronology Notes
      - 9.2 Consulting Contract and Correspondence
      - 9.3 Consulting Proposal
      - 9.4 City Directory Listings
      - 9.5 Douma, Andrew
      - 9.6 General Plan, 1959-1960
      - 9.7 Graham, Avan Tobe
      - 9.8 Historic Correspondence
      - 9.9 I.O.O.F. Mount Horeb Lodge, Number 58
      - 9.10 Markham Hotel
      - 9.11 Markham Hotel-Nomination
      - 9.12 Museum Proposal
      - 9.13 News Coverage
      - 9.14 Newspaper Articles
      - 9.15 Orange Avenue
      - 9.16 Reynolds, Sydney W.
      - 9.17 Ripon Consolidated Fire District
      - (See VHS Cassettes, Box 23) Ripon Enters the Movies, 1928
      - 9.18 Ripon Historic Survey-Main Street
      - 9.19 Ripon Historic Survey-Main Street, Research
      - 9.20 Ripon Historic Survey-Master List
      - 9.21 Ripon Historic Survey-Old Jail
      - 9.22 Ripon Historic Survey-Orange Avenue
      - 9.23 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, First Street
      - 9.24 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Second Street
      - 9.25 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Third Street
      - 9.26 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Fourth Street
      - 9.27 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Acacia Avenue
      - 9.28 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Elm Avenue
      - 9.29 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Locust Avenue
      - 9.30 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, McKee Court
      - 9.31 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Palm Avenue
      - 9.32 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Stockton Avenue
      - 9.33 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Walnut Avenue
      - 9.34 Ripon Historic Survey-Residential Neighborhoods, Photographs
      - 9.35 Ripon Historical Society
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans, Box 26) Ripon Map, 1920
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans) Ripon Map, 1927
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans) Ripon Maps, 1920
      - (See Rolled Oversize Maps and Plans) Ripon Maps, 1907, 1920, 1925, 1951
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Ripon Maps
      - 9.36 Ripon Record
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Ripon Research
      - 9.37 Ripon Research, 1846-1874
      - 9.38 Ripon Research, 1880-1900
      - 9.39 Ripon Research, 1901-1920
      - 9.40 Ripon Research, 1921-1930
      - 9.41 Ripon Research, 1966-2001
      - 9.42 Ripon Research, Tragedy 1884
      - 9.43 Ripon Research, Unsorted (1 of 2)
      - 9.44 Ripon Research, Unsorted (2 of 2)
      - 9.45 Ripon, Wisconsin
      - 9.46 Ripona
      - 9.47 Sanborn Maps
      - 9.48 Unsorted Notes and Research
  - Box 10
    - Subseries: Ripon, 1846-2004 (cont.)
      - 10.1 Photographs (1 of 3)
      - 10.2 Photographs (2 of 3)
      - 10.3 Photographs (3 of 3)
      - (See Oversize, Box 25) Ripon Historic School Photographs
      - 10.4 Slides35 mm
    - Subseries: Sacramento, 1891-2006
      Includes correspondence, newspaper photocopies and clippings, photographs, digital images, handwritten notes, applications and paperwork in support of designation as officially recognized historic resources, studies of historic properties and structures, guides to historic resources, consulting agreement, city guidelines, ordinances, enactments, and listings of historic resources.
      - 10.5 Boulevard Park
      - 10.6 Boulevard Park-Historic Context
      - 10.7 Boulevard Park-Maps
      - 10.8 Boulevard Park-Photograph Negatives, 2004
      - 10.9 Boulevard Park-Tour